All I did was love a guy.
You loved a married man.
Come home, Beth, please?
We will all be waiting for you here.
He's a good man.
- He's good...
- He's good at lying!
Have I told you
it's not just Joel he'd killed?
He killed Papa too.
You believe her?
Well, life is like that.
We're all just using each other.
Even though De Castro killed my dad,
you're the reason why there's still
no justice for his death!
You should be the one
tied and locked up.
Regina isn't the crazy one here.
- It's you.
- Fuck you, Mara.
- Stay away from me!
- Please, listen to me!
Mara!
This can't be happening!
Ben, this is all my fault!
This is all my fault... Mara...
What are you thinking of?
Us.
- Huh? Us?
- Mm.
If we're going to have a child.
Do you want one?
Do we want one?
I do.
How about you?
What if it's not meant to be?
I'm just scared that...
we won't have a peaceful life.
That's not the kind of life
I want for our child.
You know how my life was before, Ben.
We will be different.
I promise.
We will be better as parents.
This way, ma'am.
Ma'am, you're bleeding.
We need a wheelchair!
No, no.
No, I-- I need Dr. Bueno.
Doc, emergency!
Female with active bleeding!
Careful, ma'am.
Dr. Bueno, please.
Doc!
Ben, that was Mara...
Let me talk to my sister.
Mara... It's my fault, Ben.
No, Ging.
Ben, is it my fault?
- It's not your fault.
- Mara...
- That was Mara.
It wasn't Mara.
I'll fix this, okay?
- I'll fix this.
- It was Mara.
No. It was a stranger.
- It was a stranger.
- No, I saw it...
I saw it. It was me!
Stay in the car.
- I'll be back.
- I don't want to.
- I'll just talk to the police.
I'll explain to them
that it wasn't your fault.
- I don't want to.
- It's okay, Ging.
I'll explain to them it wasn't your fault.
I don't want to.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay, sir.
- I don't want to, Ben!
- I'll come and get you.
Attorney. Do you know the woman?
I don't know her.
Does your sister know her?
I doubt it. My sister has
a mental health problem.
Chief, if you have other questions,
just direct them to me.
- Okay, Attorney. Thank you.
- Okay. Thank you.
Mrs. Santos?
Ana?
There's nothing to worry.
The ultrasound showed
that you have a subchorionic hematoma.
You experienced bleeding
because a blood vessel ruptured
between your uterine lining
and the baby's gestational sac.
I'm pregnant?
Yes. Six weeks.
Bleeding during pregnancy
can be frightening, but don't worry.
We will monitor.
But I want to tell you now
that the baby is safe.
Would you like me to call Attorney?
No.
Let me be the one to...
to tell him the good news.
All right, all right.
- I'll fix your release papers.
- Okay.
So, are you ready, bro?
Yeah, I'm almost ready.
If we find any treasure,
we'll split it evenly, all right?
You won't find any treasure in Vallente.
You're more likely to find a mermaid.
You're crazy, bro.
- Let's start the engine.
- Let's go.
Please pick up.
Ana? Hello.
Ana.
They're looking for you
at the church. Where are you?
Are you going to the reception?
No.
Something happened.
What? What happened?
I'm heading home.
We can talk then.
No, Ana.
Ana, tell me what happened.
Let's talk at home, Ben.
Okay. I'm heading home. Wait for me.
I'll see you.
Take care.
- Sir.
Sir.
Good morning, sir.
- Jose.
Sir.
- What did they find out at sea?
Over here, sir.
Looks like
it was dumped a long time ago.
I agree, sir.
Okay.
I spoke to her earlier.
She said she was heading home,
but she's still not here.
And I called Katrina.
She said that Ana didn't call her.
Did something happen again?
Ana wouldn't go missing
if nothing happened.
I'll ask for help with looking for her.
Ben, it should be you who finds Ana.
Resolve it as soon as possible.
Okay.
Okay, Ana.
Shit, that's really far.
What are you doing out there?
Why are you out there?
Calm down. She's not missing.
We can't contact Beth.
We don't know where she is.
We already checked.
Her flight was not canceled.
Maybe she didn't leave.
Maybe she's still in Vallente.
She would've told us
if she wasn't leaving.
Maybe she's already here,
but she made a quick stop first.
Or maybe her phone died.
There are other explanations
aside from her going missing.
Why don't we ask Attorney Ben?
- Maybe--
No!
I mean, let me handle that.
I'll ask the people I know in Vallente.
If I don't hear anything,
we'll check with the airline
if she got on her flight.
That's all we can do for now.
Shit, Ana. Where are you?
Thank you, Nanny.
What's that?
I just picked up some of Papa's stuff.
Why'd you come at such a late hour?
Actually, ma'am,
I wanted to say goodbye to you.
Now that Papa's gone,
I have no reason to stay in Vallente.
So, you're here to ask for money?
Ah, no.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
Ma'am Imelda,
thank you so much for everything.
I am forever grateful to you
for giving my father a proper funeral.
Juancho.
Ma'am?
Just in case you need a place to stay...
you can come back anytime.
Babes, I'm here
at my contact's meeting place.
Well, well, well.
Bridgette.
Sir Ramon.
You know what?
I've changed my mind.
Why don't you bring your friend?
The one...
with big...
you-know-what.
Okay, I'll call her...
once I'm sure you'll honor the deal.
Well!
Of course I will.
Well then, let's get going.
General.
I want you to release someone
from the Malaysian operation in your area.
The one headed by Eric Mercado.
Angel. She's fair-skinned.
Her name is Angel.
Just give her to me.
No, just that one.
Just Angel.
Thanks, man.
What did he say?
That's Angel.
Well, then...
go and message your friend.
Message your friend.
Y-Yes, I'll call her.
You don't have to ask me twice.
I'll just...
call her from the restroom
while I'm freshening up.
Make it quick.
I can barely contain myself.
I'll make a call.
Hello?
I need to know the truth about my husband.
Ana...
I already know.
I know the truth.
I know that Ben is not a lawyer.
You can't deny it to me
because I already have proof.
Ben is a good lawyer.
I wouldn't send him to Vallente
if he wasn't great.
Oh, come on. I know he's great.
He's so good
that he's deceived a lot of people.
Deceived?
He helped a lot of people.
He fought for the workers
at the azucarera.
They did not lose their jobs.
But he's not a real lawyer!
Why does it matter
what you think is real or not, Ana?
Are you his client?
- I am his wife.
- Exactly!
Then why are you questioning
his credentials?
You called because
if he was hiding something from others,
he could also be hiding
something from you.
Am I right, Ana?
Tell me, Ana.
Did he ever treat you badly
as your husband?
Throughout your relationship,
did he hurt you?
Did he ever hurt you physically?
If one thing about your husband
turned out to be a lie...
does that also mean
his whole identity is a lie?
Attorney, a lie is a lie.
You knew,
so you should pay for it as well.
Good day. May I ask you something?
I am looking for someone.
Have you seen this woman
pass by here?
No.
Are you sure?
No, sir.
All right. Thank you.
- Okay, then.
- Excuse me.
May I ask you something?
It's just that...
I'm looking for this woman.
She was just here earlier.
- Where did she go?
- She went in that direction.
- Yes, that way.
- Thank you!
We will be better as parents.
Are you there?
Are you really there, my child?
My child...
What am I going to do with you?
I don't even know what to do with myself.
I'm sorry,
we're not ready for you.
Ana!
Even if you report us to the cops...
nothing will happen.
Boss Eric can just as easily
abduct you again.
Look at me!
Remember this.
You may be free now,
but we still have eyes on you.
Now, get lost!
Go!
Take off your clothes.
What are you waiting for?
Take it off!
Hey, any updates?
We already let Angel out.
She's out already.
Okay.
You heard him, right?
Thanks, man.
Go and call your friend.
Wait!
I haven't... I haven't
seen her yet. I need to check.
Besides, wouldn't--
Call her now!
You know, if she's not coming...
I'll just have you instead.
She's on her way now!
Hey, hey, hey! I did you a favor already.
Your friend is now free! So now...
it's your turn to do me a favor!
No! Help!
Bridgette! Hold on, girl!
Please stay strong, girl! We're close!
Come here!
- Carlota! Help me!
Help me!
Please stop!
Help me! Help, please!
Put your hands up!
Stop what you're doing!
- Bridge!
- Carlota!
- What's going on?
- Put your hands up!
Shh!
- It's me.
- Diane?
- Okay? It's me.
- Diane...
Diane...
Shh. Don't cry anymore.
- How did you find me?
- You're safe now.
- They're following me!
- No.
- I'm right here. I'm here.
- They're following me.
Come, let's go.
Miss.
Miss, is he Brian Robles?
Yes.
He's my brother.
Brian!
Ana!
What are you doing here?
How did you know that I was here?
Ana, I asked so many people!
I was so worried about you.
Luckily, someone saw you.
What's happening?
Why didn't you attend the wedding?
I just didn't want to.
Ana...
you would kill if there was something
wrong with your clients' clothes.
This has never happened before.
People change.
Ana, can you tell me
what's happening, please? Please.
A spouse
doesn't have to know everything, right?
No, I think... I think this one...
you have to tell me
why you're here and what's going on.
I'm worried about you.
So, there are things
that we should and shouldn't know,
and you're the one who gets to decide?
Is this about me?
It's always about you, love.
Everything... is about you.
Ana...
Ana! Ana?
Ana, what's happening? Ana?
Tell everyone
that we'll have
a large-scale search operation on the sea.
- Sir?
- Yes.
We'll do it in the area
where Brian Robles's body was found.
We'll gather all the clues
related to the case, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, go! Hurry up.
You're pregnant?
How are you feeling, Ana?
Ana, I'm so happy.
You're pregnant.
Why now?
There were a lot of chances before.
Why did I have to be pregnant now?
It's okay.
How can we be good parents
when we don't even have a good marriage?
Fine.
Maybe it's just right
that I became pregnant right now.
So my child would grow up knowing
how big a liar their father is.
Ana. Ana!
Ana, please stop!
Ana! Ana, stop!
What you're doing will affect our child!
- Ana!
- And what about you?
Do you think
that will not affect our child?
What have I done?
You lie!
You lie and you lie every single time!
You're not a real lawyer!
You're just pretending to be one!
What?
Oh, come on, just stop! Stop!
Nobody can hear you!
It's just us here!
Are you still going to lie to me?
Ben... just be honest.
You didn't pass the bar.
You didn't graduate.
I saw your yearbook!
I checked your IBP number.
Ben...
you're a fraud!
But here you are in Vallente...
it's like you're this superhero lawyer!
I can't believe
I thought I was going crazy!
I thought my suspicions were wrong.
But it's you!
You fooled me!
Who are you?
I don't even know who you are!
- Who are you, huh? Who are you?
- Ana, stop.
- Who are you?
- Ana, stop. Ana, stop.
Okay! Okay. Okay.
It's true.
But Ana...
I defended the weak.
I championed for those
who can't fight just because they're poor.
I served the farmers.
Ana, I've built a company
that will support and defend them.
I'm a better lawyer than others.
No, that doesn't make it right.
Okay, I went to law school!
I went to law school,
but I couldn't take the bar.
Because I was charged with fraud.
I was involved
in something that dealt with money.
In short, I did not graduate.
So I had to use
another person's credentials
just so I can keep going.
'Cause I had Regina.
I wanted to continue caring for Regina.
And I had a dream.
And my dream was to become a lawyer.
Just so we could have a fighting chance.
That's it, Ana.
That's why I did what I did.
You used me?
Did you really love me, Ben?
Or did you just use me
to legitimize your life?
Ana, listen.
I love you so much.
I love you so much, Ana.
My love for you has no lies.
How? How can I believe that
when I can't trust anything about you?
I can't do this.
I'm done.
Wait.
Just because I'm not a real lawyer?
Because you... betrayed me.
And now that
you've dragged me into all of your lies,
I need to do something to correct them.
Okay, let's go.
Are you sure you're all right?
How is Angel doing?
She's getting better.
I took her to her mother.
She'll message us when she's all settled.
Girl, hey.
It's all okay now. We're all okay.
Here.
You're right.
What matters is...
Angel's now safe.
And so are you.
We're all together again.
We're still not complete.
Beth's not with us yet.
Diane,
what did you and Beth last talk about?
The last thing she told me
was that she was coming home.
I talked with Megan earlier.
She said Beth still hasn't contacted them.
We just wrapped up one problem,
now here comes another one.
Now, it's Beth.
I'm sorry, but...
I have a bad feeling about this.
Go and move the second body now.
Take it to the morgue.
Sir! Sir!
They found another body!
- That's already the third one.
- It is, sir.
How many more bodies
did they throw into the sea?
Hi, Ana. Sorry, I look tired.
But look at this place.
Look at that place.
Look at this.
So this could be your receiving area
for your clients.
And then...
here.
This... this one...
This one will be your workshop.
And...
the master's bedroom.
There's a room next to it.
Now that could be the baby's room.
Wow.
That man's effort as a husband...
Are you really siding with him, Ma?
He lied.
Why, Silvana?
Are you perfect?
Have you never lied in your life
to demand a hundred percent honesty
from your husband?
Silvana... he did that out of love.
Why is it so easy for you to say
he lied out of love?
How can it be love if there are lies?
Ana, we don't live in a perfect world.
There can never be
complete honesty in a relationship.
Yeah, but you make it sound like
what Ben did wasn't a big deal.
That's eight years, Ma.
He hid that from me for eight long years.
He fooled people for nearly a decade...
by posing as a lawyer.
So what if he isn't a lawyer?
He did a better job
protecting other people...
than actual lawyers
who are either stupid or corrupt.
No, the end does not justify the means.
It's a noble deception, Silvana.
When has lying been a good thing?
You should know, Ma.
Weren't you furious at Papa
when he betrayed you?
He left me for another woman.
That's completely different!
No. They're the same.
They lied about different things,
but they still lied.
Look, Ana,
all I'm saying is that...
he did it all out of love. Okay?
Ma, listen to yourself.
I'm not saying what he did was right.
But your husband truly loves you.
Not everyone experiences
that kind of love.
Did he hurt you?
Did he ever lay a hand on you?
He didn't, right?
What kind of life will my child have?
You and Ben can still give your child
a good life...
if you guys will stay together.
No!
No.
I can't stomach what Ben did.
Okay, Silvana.
What do you want to do?
You want to leave him?
Look, Ana.
If you can wholeheartedly tell me...
that your life
would be better without Ben,
that you'll be happier without him...
then by all means, go! Leave!
But if not...
please, think twice.
Thrice!
I don't know what to do...
This is wrong.
What's the point of doing what's right
if your life is miserable?
One victim suffered head trauma,
while the other two had
slash wounds to the neck.
All of the victims were wrapped
and the knots used to bind them
were identical.
So there is a pattern. It's possible
that the same person killed them all.
Oh, Ana.
What brings you here?
Did something happen?
You need to know something about Ben.
Please don't tell me it's another scandal.
The issue with his sister
hasn't even blown over yet.
That's just one of his lies.
What are you saying?
Did Ben hurt you?
He's a fraud.
He's not a real lawyer.
He's a fake!
Before he arrived at Vallente,
he was already pretending to be a lawyer.
This is for everyone's sake.
I represented you
in these contracts and cases...
that I won for you.
Now, when they find out
I'm not really a lawyer,
it will affect all of this.
You've got some nerve
putting us in this situation.
We trusted you.
And I delivered, didn't I, sir?
I don't know
where this arrogance comes from.
If I planned
to rob you of money and power,
I never would've told you the truth.
I would've turned my back on you
a long time ago.
I've been very loyal.
And I expect the same.
Mariano.
Our reputation is on the line!
You heard the man.
Enough, Mona.
Good job, Ben.
Wait.
You knew all along?
No. This is new information.
But to be honest, so what?
I mean, everything he does
is for the good of the azucarera.
What?
You're just going to let this slide?
- Auntie!
- My dear...
sometimes,
technicalities don't really matter.
Especially if you look at the big picture.
Wha-- What big picture?
They'd have to reopen
cases he won for the azucarera.
Including ownership of the land...
that took years to fight in court.
We can't afford that.
I know it's hard to accept.
Especially you're his wife.
But please...
don't tell anyone about this.
What?
This is all for the best. For all of us.
Do you understand me?
- Ana, I'm--
- No, no.
You scheming bastard.
You planned everything.
You even got the Saguils involved
in your lies.
And you want me to believe...
that you didn't use me?
Oh, my God.
Ana, I'm not using you.
I swear.
- Ana--
- No, don't touch me!
You're full of lies.
Don't follow me.
Ana, Ana-- Please.
Ana. Ana!
Ana. Ana, please.
We'll have a hard time
identifying the victims.
They were submerged in water for too long.
What are we going to do, sir?
We can compare them
against the missing persons list.
Maybe we can find a match
based on their height
or other identifying features
that could give us a lead.
This one has tattoos.
This one too.
I don't know, sir.
Are tattoos our only lead?
No.
We have to start somewhere.
I know it's hard,
but we have to figure this out.
We don't know if we're dealing
with one person or a group.
We need to make sure
there won't be any more victims.
Copy, sir.
When was the last time you saw Beth?
On the day of her flight to Manila.
She was moving out her stuff.
What did she tell you?
Did she recommend this apartment to you?
Ah, yes.
She told me that
since she was going home already,
I could take over the lease.
Even though you're friends with Beth,
you can't use her deposit.
What deposit?
Yes. Didn't she tell you
that she still has a month's deposit?
Well, I can't blame her.
If I were in her shoes,
I'd also get out of here.
Why? What happened to Beth?
She doesn't really talk
about her personal life.
Rumor has it,
it's because of Doña Imelda's doing.
Doña Imelda?
Hold on, Ana.
Why do you insist on driving yourself?
We have a driver!
Ma, if you don't want to come with me
to my OB-GYN appointment, it's okay.
I can go by myself.
Nonsense.
I'm already dressed up.
Come on, come on. Let's go, let's go.
- My goodness.
- Ma'am?
- What?
- Someone's here for Miss Ana.
Is it Ben?
No, ma'am.
It's her.
Cedes, you're not supposed to tell anyone
where my daughter is.
She doesn't want to be found!
What were you thinking?
Tell me what you need.
We're worried about Beth.
Her siblings and I can't reach her.
And you think I know where she is?
You and your friends are unbelievable.
You might know where she is
because of what happened.
Yes, I know about that.
And I also know the rumors going around
that your mother did something
to my friend.
And now you're going after my mom?
If you knew what really happened,
you wouldn't have come here.
I was humiliated.
She caused so much trouble.
Which is why I had no choice
but to come here.
My friend's a nobody.
Who knows what you could've done to her
because of her foolishness?
Beth means nothing to me now, okay?
If you won't tell me where she is,
I'll have to talk to Attorney Ben.
Then ask him.
I don't know where he is.
Huh?
You're not together anymore?
Is that all you need?
You may go now. I have somewhere to be.
Those CCTV cameras don't work?
No, sir. They've been broken for a while.
Do you have a list of clients
who use these yachts?
We do, sir. But we don't have records
for all passengers.
We only have records of those they report.
Okay.
We're checking areas accessible by boat.
Have any yacht owners
been acting suspiciously?
We have a lot of shady clients, sir.
These are rich folks we're talking about.
They bring all kinds of people here.
Like who?
Uh... women, sir.
This yacht is owned by a doctor.
That's where he performs his "procedures."
What about this one?
What's this one hiding?
Nothing, sir.
That's Attorney Ben's boat.
Attorney Ben? Ben Santos?
Yes, Ben Santos. Spotless, right?
Only Attorney Ben
keeps his yacht this clean.
But he's not here often.
Fear has swept
the town of Vallente...
- What is going on?
- ...as bodies were found
- in the last few days.
- Nanny?
- Nanny, water, please.
- Okay, ma'am.
Authorities recovered the bodies
after divers found them at sea.
That's a lot of bodies!
What's happening to Vallente?
That dock is nearby!
A relative has identified
the body of Brian Robles.
So far,
three bodies have been recovered
by the police.
Relatives have identified
the remains of the victims.
They have been identified
as Danny Pascual and Joel Geraldo.
The police are doing everything we can
to help the victims' relatives.
An investigation is underway to determine
if there's a connection
between the victims' deaths.
We have not ruled out the possibility
that a group or an individual
is behind these crimes.
Ma'am, here's your water.
Brian is gone, Ana.
- Ben!
- No, I just saw Brian.
- He stopped by our house.
- Ana.
- He's going through something.
- No, he's not.
Ben's money is all he's after.
Miss Ana, someone's looking for you.
- Oh.
- Miss Ana Madrigal-Santos?
Yes.
Danny Pascual from DPEvents.
Hello, how can I help you?
Hi, could I interview you
about your husband?
It's for the Saguils' event.
Ben killed my husband.
Regina!
With how long
I've been looking after Regina,
- she's told me a lot...
- Did you see it?
...about the things
Ben does to other people.
No.
But I know he did it.
Have I told you
it's not just Joel that he killed?
He killed Papa too.
I saw it with my own eyes.
We're worried about Beth.
Her siblings and I can't reach her.
Which is why I had no choice
but to come here.
My friend's a nobody.
Who knows what you could've done to her
because of her foolishness?
I promise to be your safe space
when the world feels heavy.
To be your home
when things are uncertain.
I give you my love eternal.
My loyalty.
To keep choosing you
again and again...
in every version of tomorrow.
Taste it.
You want to do it yourself?
Okay.
If you don't want me to feed you...
Please, Beth.
Eat.
Okay.
Let's eat.
I need trust. I need loyalty.
Be careful.
Be careful, Ana.
- Ana!
Your husband is a monster.
No!
- Stop!
How sordid.
All these victims are connected to you.
Do you have evidence
that connects me to these murders?
Ben, I know!
I'm not leaving Vallente
without my friend!
- No! Ana!